Alarm, frogs, greens, I'd sooze like a pro The two pairs of
eyes say "Come on, let's
go!"
The leash is a mess, they're tangled again I know they need
to go, just don't know when
No thought be yet, but they don't care They're sippin'
every bowl, every tree, every
chair I swear they're puttin' drab feet to the
park Damn, no way, we only tell me all these breaths
Why I Two dogs, one mince, no beefs
And the reggae sets up for a master beef Sunday on five,
show up aboard the daily
parade I'll decide, watch, breath, for my big night
faves Two dogs, one mince, no beefs
Neighbors wave, I pretend I'm the console But B.O.'s like
an M.T.O.
Juki's biting the mailman's shoe I'm yelling their names
like a fuck, but that's
who Yes, this is an exercise, this is urban combat
I'm Don Ditch, blooters, rollers, and a psycho jack
It's the days I dream of the robot fuck And then they look
at me and I just shut up
Two dogs, one mince, no beefs I am so stretched like a
Jesus beast
On the ground, barge out of a cave parade Every morning, P.
L. is one day and one day
Two dogs, one mince, no beefs I love it like Koopa Day, boy
it's sane
Chasing swirls like it's egg cocaine And when we're home, I
'm gay
They're just fresh and stored Why, then it will sum a civil
war
Two dogs, one mince, no beefs Call the U.N. for a parking
cease
But tomorrow at dawn, we'll be out again Just a guy, his
dog's send, zero-send
Two dogs, one mince, no beefs